PENNY: Hey, Leonard?
- The hair products are Sheldon's.
PENNY:
Okay.
- Um, can I ask you a favor?
- A favor?
Sure, you could ask me a favor.
I would do you a favor for you.
- It's okay if you say no.
- Oh, I'll probably say yes.
(Penny:)It's just not the kind of thing
you ask a guy you just met.
(Penny:)Wow.
(Sheldon:)I really think we should examine
the chain of causality here.
- Must we?
- Event A:
(Sheldon:)A beautiful woman
stands naked in our shower.
Event B: We drive halfway across town
to retrieve a television set...
(Sheldon:)...from the aforementioned woman's
ex-boyfriend.
Query: On what plane of existence
is there even a semi-rational link...
(Sheldon:)...between these events?
She asked me to do her a favor, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Well, that may be the proximal cause
of our journey...
...but we both know it exists
in contradistinction...
...to the higher-level distal cause.
- Which is?
- You think with your penis.